{
    "id": "af21d97450584c76aaeada0a2c47a2b5",
    "title": "For, To and So That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I talked to the shy girl ............................ she wouldn't feel left out.",
            "description": "We use 'so' to indicate the result or effect.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7056f111e8d14688ad151e1e3b667bb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped at the pub .............................. a drink.",
            "description": "Only the infinitive can be used to express a person's purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "to have",
                "for having",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "62b892df22144997b262d9930bd3d23f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped at the pub ........................ a drink.",
            "description": "'For' can indicate purpose when it is followed by a noun. It cannot be used before a verb to express purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "for having",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a4e6dbd13794f80b18aab713acbe63b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to Canada ............................ my brother.",
            "description": "Only the infinitive can be used to express a person's purpose. 'For' can indicate it only when it is followed by a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "for seeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f663cc535a7849be9a9c178817fb4ad2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What do I need to get ............................... dinner?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0469262642b24391ac08cdd28fdbf69b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sort your rubbish .............................. recycling.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97f2ddc97f1545e4884d37d602f01a5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I took the phone back to the store ....................... a replacement.",
            "description": "Only the infinitive can be used to express a person's purpose. 'For' can indicate it only when it is followed by a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "for getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b7195d8e347440a8fef4f782627ee11"
        },
        {
            "question": "We started early ........................... we wouldn't be late.",
            "description": "In an informal style that can be dropped after so.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ef975d2930cc4a7fa6e9be88f830776f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You need to be over 18 ......................... that film.",
            "description": "Only the infinitive can be used to express a person's purpose. 'For' can indicate it only when it is followed by a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "for watching",
                "to watch",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcb897ea7be24983a95fdbbee3805498"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am leaving early today ........................... the rush hour traffic.",
            "description": "Only the infinitive can be used to express a person's purpose. 'For' can indicate it only when it is followed by a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "for avoiding",
                "to avoid",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "406d90f771d143e8a6f0295c58c90a38"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am putting the meat in the oven now, .......................... it will be ready by eight o'clock.",
            "description": "We use 'so that' before a clause to indicate purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "for",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "53b243a1a9064e27b70be586bb95d890"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am angry with you ........................... me up.",
            "description": "For can be followed by an ing form after a description of a reaction to explain the behavior that caused it. ",
            "answers": [
                "to wake",
                "for waking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1bddbd3aff64e2998c50fd862143cab"
        }
    ]
}